Mosarimi 15

Reykjavik, Postal Code: 112, Iceland

897-8301

antonheimdal@protonmail.com

github.com/aheimdal

Anton H. Heimdal

Goals

I want to earn experience and accumulate skills in the computer programming industry to work towards financial freedom to have a better live set up for me and my son. To further my skill set I will use Udemy and other online platforms to improve my knowledge in the field of programming and designing.



EXPERIENCE

Smakranar ehf, Reykjavik - Crane Operator

May 2017 - PRESENT

• I have licenses to operate small cranes and drive trucks with trailers.

Window Cleaning Contractor, Reykjavik — Contractor Window Cleaner July 2019 - PRESENT

• Extra job to pay the bills to be able to stay in school.

Malbikunarstodin Colas ehf, Hafnarfjordur - Group leader

July 2017 - August 2017

- Worked as a group supervisor
- As a truck driver as well as machine operator

EDUCATION

University of Iceland, Reykjavik — Bachelor's Degree

August 2017 - February 2021 (Graduating)

University of Reykjavik, Reykjavik - Students Degree

August 2014 - December 2015

Finished a Students degree equivalent in 3 semesters

Extra Courses taken outside of school

Got my truck and machine licence in a Driving Educational school called New Driving school (Nýji Ökuskólinn)

Languages

I speak Icelandic (Native language), English fluently, German (Basic), Danish (Basic) and Norwegian (Basic).

Computer Knowledge

I have good knowledge on operating systems like windows and Linux and I have good grasp on C#, Python, Java, Javascript, ATOM, Angular, Node.js JSON. All this knowledge has been accumulated through my school work at the University of Iceland.

In my spare time I have been learning on the Unity engine with the help of Udemy courses.

I also have a good understanding on how Github works and how to use it in projects.

Personal Projects

I am currently working on both a personalized website and a Timereport app. Originally got into programming to make games.

Recommendations

Erlingur Snær Erlingsson +354 699 4241 (Smakranar ehf, Manager)